and hello again I said I was going to do
a video on just these two it'll be much
shorter um these are some uh insurance
companies that are still in business
credential very very business very long
time uh take a look at these and like
Mike was saying when he was auctioning
his office look at the artwork of these
how much effort they put into making
just a policy form they give to somebody
look attractive and make it look like
man I really want to open that up and
see what's in there I really want to do
business with these people I have that
one and I have this
one but the treat is I open them up so
you could see at least uh the inside
Pages because if you open them up uh
further it's
just
um provisions of the loan and how you
pay it where you pay it what happens if
you can't pay it and I'll give you a
date but look at the back page of this
one these are going to go in a
frame with uh the museum Quality Glass
matted and so it's going to be a bit
before I get them done but I want to
preserve these the best I can they've
already got some staining on them of
course from the age U this one right
here the blue one that's from
1930 it's not as spectacular as the next
one but I want to to show you
[Applause]
anyway look at
that April 7th 1930 and you go
down and amount of insurance
$215 weekly premium
25 I want to have that type of Premium
on
my oo
ah my battery's going dead hopefully I
can get this done won't be as bright but
um that is cool
right very nice so I'll fold that up uh
neatly carefully now look at this one
before my battery goes
dead same credential look at that look
at
that nothing really on the back page let
me turn this
over now look at that
is that class or
what $500
Insurance beneficiary wife of the
insured so this
is oh maybe life insurance I I hadn't
really looked at it until right
now
um 19 1831 but look at that though
before my battery sorry I have to cut it
shorter but my battery is going to go
dead any second
now isn't that nice look at the the the
quality of this even the paper is held
on there's a couple little tiny things I
might have repaired as I'm having them
framed take it to a conservator I know U
it'll do something for me but very nice
this is the kind of stuff that I like to
get because it can also be if used
carefully uh visual movie props you know
uh just things for other videos that I
might do uh later on uh maybe replicate
him and you know uh do some things with
them as far as Productions go anyways I
hope you enjoyed it and I hope everybody
had a nice Christmas and I hope
everybody has a safe New Year's
celebration uh go ahead and give
somebody you love a call and just let
them know that you're thinking about him
probably mean the world to him and U
we'll see you on my next video hopefully
more hopefully soon thanks for watching